LEON NICHOLLS: 大家好  我是Leon Nicholls
LEON NICHOLLS: Hi, my name is Leon Nicholls.
我是Google Cast的一名开发大使
I'm a Developer Advocate for Google Cast.
在这里我将会告诉你关于Google Cast SDK for Android的一些信息
I'm here to tell you about the Google Cast SDK for Android.
Google Cast SDK支持Android IOS
The Google Cast SDK supports Android, iOS,
以及桌面版的Chrome浏览器平台
and desktop Chrome platforms.
针对这些平台开发的应用程序都能
Apps developed for these platforms can all
与任何Google Cast设备进行交互  比如Chromecast
interact with any Google Cast device, such as Chromecast.
Google Cast sender端
The Google Cast sender application
是指运行在移动设备或笔记本的应用程序
refers to an app running on a mobile device or laptop,
receiver端是指一个HTML应用程序
and the receiver application refers to an HTML application
它运行在Chromecast或其他Google Case receiver设备上
running on Chromecast or other Google Cast receiver devices.
Google Case SDK的发行版
The release of the Google Cast SDK
是为Cast应用程序的开发者们提供的公共API
is the public API for developers of Cast applications.
从现在开始  开发者们通过使用
From now on, developers are in control
新的Google Cast SDK 开发者控制台
of releasing the Cast apps by using the new Google Cast SDK
来控制Cast应用程序的发布流程
developer console.
Google Cast SDK现在是Android的Google Play服务的一部分
The Google Cast SDK is now a part of Android's Google Play
并且将在所有的Cast应用程序之间共享
services, and will be shared across all Cast apps.
让我们来看看一个Cast sender应用的典型生命周期
Let's take a look at the typical life cycle of a Cast sender app.
当sender程序启动后  Cast设备
When the sender app is launched, Cast devices
需要在本地网络被发现
need to be discovered on the local network.
一旦用户选择了一个设备  sender程序
Once the user selects a device, the sender app
将会连接这个设备并启动receiver程序
will connect to that device and launch the receiver app.
然后sender程序创建一个消息通道
The sender app then creates a message channel
到receiver程序  以用来发送和接收消息
to the receiver app to send and receive messages.
用户也可以从这些设备上断开连接
The user can also disconnect from that device.
使应用程序支持Cast的第一步操作是添加一个Cast按钮
The first step in supporting Cast in an app is to add the Cast button.
有三个选择  MediaRouter ActionBar提供者
There are three choices-- the MediaRouter ActionBar provider,
MediaRouter按钮  或自定义按钮
the MediaRouter button, or a custom button.
我们建议提供者因为它是最简单的整合
We recommend the provider since that's the easiest integration.
对于ActionBar  Cast按钮需要添加添加到菜单中
The Cast button has to be added to the menu for the ActionBar,
或者是activity布局资源文件中
or to the activity layout resource file.
创建一个MeidaRouter选择器的优点是
The advantage to create a MediaRouter selector, which
它将会下拉显示的设备是
will fall to devices to discover only
仅仅可以运行你的应用的Cast设备
Cast devices that can run your app.
选择器是当这个activity启动时附加到Cast按钮上的
The selector is attached to the Cast button when the activity starts.
这里有个例子是关于
Here is an example of how easy it
在ActionBar上添加一个Cast按钮是多么的简单
is to add a Cast button to the ActionBar
只需在你的menu XML文件中使用MediaRouter ActionBar提供者
[? compat ?] using the MediaRouter ActionBar provider
就可以了
in your menu XML.
其他的集成Cast按钮的方式
Other ways of integrating the Cast button
可以在通过MediaRouter支持库生成的文档中找到
is documented by the MediaRouter support library.
在这个activity启动时  sender程序也需要
The sender app also has to tell the MediaRouter to start
通过添加一个回调函数来告诉MediaRouter
discovery of Cast devices by adding
启动发现Cast设备
a callback when the activity starts.
当用户从Cast菜单选择了一个设备
The app will be informed by the MediaRouter
这个应用将通过MediaRouter被通知
when the user has selected a device from the Cast menu.
最佳的做法是  当发现不再需要的时候
As a best practice, remove the callback
移除这个回调函数  以节约电池的使用
when discovery is no longer needed, to conserve battery usage.
这里有个例子是关于如何为MediaRouter添加一个回调函数
Here's an example of how to add a callback to the MediaRouter
以启动设备发现的
to start device discovery.
用户选择的设备是从回调函数数据中提取的
The device the user has selected is extracted from the callback data.
现在sender程序知道用户选择了哪个Cast设备
Now that the sender app knows which Cast device the user has selected,
启动这个receiver程序涉及到几个步骤
launching the receiver app involves a few steps.
sender程序需要使用GoogleAPIClient Cast
The sender app needs to connect to Google Play Services using
连接到Google Play Services
the GoogleAPIClient Cast.
之后程序使用Cast.CastAPI
Then the app uses the Cast.CastAPI
启动receiver程序  其中会使用到从开发者控制台中
Cast to launch the receiver app using the app ID obtained
获得的应用程序ID
from the Developer Console.
一旦这个receiver程序启动后
Once the receiver app has launched,
sender程序就可以对receiver创建一个多媒体消息管道或
the sender can create a media message channel or a custom
自定义消息管道
message channel to the receiver.
这个应用需要处理不同的回调函数
The app has to handle various callbacks
关于应用和管道的状态
about the application and the channel status.
这里有个例子是关于当sender程序已经连接到Google Play服务后
Here's an example of how to launch the receiver
是如何启动receiver程序的
app once the sender app has connected to Google Play services.
结果回调函数需要以启动状态和
The result callback is invoked with the launch status
应用程序元数据作为参数进行调用
and the application metadata.
注意在Cast应用程序的整个生命周期
Note the same asynchronous callback model
都使用相同的异步调用模型
is used throughout the life cycle of a Cast app.
为了在receiver端播放媒体  sender程序
To play media on the receiver, the sender app
需要创建一个具有媒体流数据URL的MediaInfo实例
has to create a MediaInfo instance with the URL of the media stream.
然后RemoteMediaPlayer
The RemoteMediaPlayer Cast is then
被用来在receiver端加载这些媒体流数据
used to load that media stream on the receiver.
之后sender程序使用RemoteMediaPlayer
The sender app then accepts commands such as play and pause
接受诸如播放和暂停等命令
using the RemoteMediaPlayer.
sender程序需要在重放时
The sender app has to handle callbacks about the media
执行关于媒体状态的回调函数
status during playback.
最后  让我们看一个例子
Finally, let's take a look at an example
关于如何为视频流创建一个MediaInfo实例
of how to create a MediaInfo instance for a video stream.
视频流在receiver端使用RemoteMediaPlayer实例
The video stream is loaded on the receiver using
来加载
the RemoteMediaPlayer instance.
ResultCallback以加载命令状态作为参数来调用
The ResultCallback is invoked with the load command status.
你可以在developers.google.com/cast
You can get more details about the Google Cast SDK
获取关于Google Cast SDK的更多详细信息
at developers.google.com/cast.
同样重要的是要看一下Cast Design Checklist
It's also important to take a look at the Cast Design
这里有一些应用的设计原则
Checklist, which has design implications for your app.
我们也开源了一些示例Cast应用程序
We've also opened source sample Cast apps
你可以用来作为参考
that you can use as a reference.
如果你有人任何开发者的问题  请在Stack Overflow上贴出来吧
If you have any developer questions, post those on Stack Overflow.
欢迎在Google+上加入我们的Google Cast开发者社区
Join our Google Cast Developers Community on Google+.
Happy Casting
Happy Casting.